budde.com.au 2018-03-14

# Privacy Policy - BuddeComm

  * 
  * Policies / Disclaimer
  * Privacy
  * Copyright / User Licenses
  * Email & Spam
  * Purchasing

Paul Budde Communication Pty Ltd (trading as BuddeComm) is dedicated to the protection of individual privacy issues and committed to the responsible handling of personal information online. Our mission is to promote and foster an ethical marketplace and your privacy is extremely important to us. Set out below are details of our online information practices, adhering to the guidelines as specified by the Government's National Privacy Principles (NPP). 

### The information we collect:

When you register as a member of our Web site we collect a certain amount of personal information from you so that you can download Web reports efficiently from our research database as required. As specified by NPP, we only collect personal information as required for our business activities with you. All personal information is contained internally and kept confidential and all sensitive information is encrypted. We use your return e-mail addresses only to respond to incoming e-mails and we certainly do not share such addresses or any other personally identifiable information with any outside parties for any reasons. This information is reviewed regularly and whatever is not specifically required for business activities is discarded permanently. 

### Our commitment to data security: 

To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. All information is permanently and immediately deleted upon request from you at any time. 

### E-commerce security guarantee: 

BuddeComm uses SecurePay's Internet Payment Gateway to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card transactions over the Internet. Confidential information including client credit card details are encrypted the moment they are transmitted from the client's browser to the banking network using industry standard SSL 128-bit RC4 encryption technology.  

A client's credit card details are not stored anywhere on the Internet and the only company who has access to this data is the merchant's bank. The bank also sends confirmation information via the same encryption technology back to the client's browser. These secure processes provide clients with peace of mind when purchasing online.

### Purchase with Confidence

> Paul is by far, the leading telecommunications analyst in Australia. Not only is his company's research first class and timely, it is superbly contextual to the complexities of today's modern media and communications technology. He is always extremely generous in sharing his knowledge with others and has a great ability to connect people together and be a thought leader on topics of National interest such as the NBN, FttH and Smart Grids. 
> 
> **Bruce Duyshart, Director Strategic Technology, Lend Lease**

### News & Views

Have the latest telecommunications industry news delivered to your inbox by subscribing to Paul's FREE weekly News & Views.
